Guide to the National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case Records TAM.174
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case Records
1944-2005
1974-1997
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case
Hittner, Daniel
TAM.174
19 Linear Feet in 17 record cartons, 1 tall manuscript box, 1 card box, and 3 oversize folders in shared housing.
4 film reels
2 websites in 2 archived websites.
2 audiocassettes
3 sound discs (cd)
1 sound discs (vinyl)
A number of national organizations were created in response to the Rosenberg and Sobell espionage cases in which Julius and Ethel Rosenberg were convicted and sentenced to death and Morton Sobell was sentenced to 30 years in prison. Following the conviction of the Rosenbergs in 1951, the National Committee to Secure Justice in the Rosenberg Case (NCSJRC) was formed. In the early 1970s Michael and Robert Meeropol, the Rosenberg's sons, sued the FBI under the Freedom of Information Act, and won the release of hundreds of thousands of previously secret documents pertaining to their parents' case. The National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case (NCRRC) was formed in conjunction with the proceedings of the suit. The NCRRC sought to exonerate the Rosenbergs, prove their innocence, and push for acknowledgement from the United States government that there had been a miscarriage of justice in the trial proceedings. The collection contains materials spanning the years 1944-2005, with the bulk of material dating from 1974-1997. The majority of materials in the collection were created in the process of the outreach and publicity work that the organization did, and include correspondence and promotional materials. Promotional materials consist of research files (e.g. court transcripts, FOIA documents, newspaper clippings, and promotional materials from other organizations), article and newsletter drafts, newsletters, newsletter mock-ups, press releases, flyers, event programs and planning materials, pamphlets, booklets, photographic prints and negatives, and ads. Related to these promotional materials and research files are works and publications created in response to, or inspired by, the Rosenberg case. These include plays, an opera, music, manuscripts, theses, and books from writers, researchers, and students. These artistic and academic creations include manuscripts, bound materials, cassette tapes, audio CDs, vinyl records, and a VHS tape. To a lesser extent, there are administrative records such as meeting minutes, agendas, memos, event planning documents, fundraising reports, local committee finances, and financial reports.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case in 1995; additional materials were donated by Daniel Hittner, Director, in 2006. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 1991.014 and NPA 2006.010.
Websites were initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2009 as part of the Communism, Socialism, Trotskyism Web Archive. In 2014, crawling of the website was discontinued. In 2015, these websites were migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website.
Related Archival Materials
Related collections documenting the work of the Committee to Re-open the Rosenberg Case and its various renditions include:
The Register of the Ethel and Julius Rosenberg Papers, 1952-1979 (MSS 008) at the Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research
The Robert Altman Archive: Business and Financial Records, Legal Series and Chronological Files, 1969-2007 at the Special Collections Research Center at the University of Michigan Library
The Julius and Ethel Rosenberg Archive, the David and Emily Almon Collection, and the Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell Collection, all at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center at Boston University
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Arrangement
The National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case Records is arranged into four series:
Series I. Adminstrative and Financial Records
Series II. Correspondence
Series III. Promotional Materials
Series IV. Archived Website
Regarding the arrangement of the collection, it should also be noted that the types of materials generated during the Committee's work are somewhat blurred across their activities. While there is a correspondence series with letters between the NCRRC and their supporters, sponsors and donors, committee members, local committees, institutions, and news outlets, correspondence is also a part of the the promotional materials series. Letter exchanges between the Committee and various stakeholders or political or social figures may be distributed through the NCRRC's newsletter. Some folders between series are also titled similarly, but contain different types of material and were grouped by the Committee differently. A folder called "Jewish Currents" may exist in both Series II and Series III due to the different types of materials they contain and the different ways the NCRRC used that information. Local committees are similarly represented in the collection in both Series I and Series III due to the varying purposes of the materials collected by the organization - in Series I, to document the work that local committees are doing, and in Series III, to collect the instances of publicity that the local committees are getting in newspapers.
Appraisal
Appraisal decisions made prior to 2019 are not documented. During processing in 2019, duplicates of newsletters, articles, newspaper clipping photocopies, and other distributable material were deaccessioned. Out-of-scope materials were also deaccessioned, such as the personal papers of the NCRRC's long-time director, Aaron Katz. Committee materials such as contribution and donation forms, tax documents, receipts and invoices, office lease documentation, job applications, and post office forms were deaccessioned. Extensive duplicates of Committee materials were also discarded.
Historical Note
A number of national and local organizations were created in response to the Rosenberg and Sobell espionage cases in which Julius and Ethel Rosenberg were convicted and sentenced to death, and Morton Sobell was sentenced to 30 years in prison. These national and local organizations engaged in community and political activism to defend, save, secure justice for, and secure clemency for the Rosenbergs. Following the conviction of the Rosenbergs and Sobell in 1951, the journalist William A. Reuben wrote a series of investigative articles for the National Guardian, and was involved in the formation of the National Committee to Secure Justice in the Rosenberg Case (NCSJRC) with David and Emily Alman. Their grassroots campaign focused on preventing the couple's execution. They organized mass protests, letter campaigns, clemency petitions, fundraisers for legal fees and child care for the Rosenberg's two young sons, and the creation and distribution of publications to present new evidence to raise questions about the legitimacy of the Rosenberg trial and death sentence.
The controversy surrounding the Rosenbergs' sentencing continued after their executions, and the grassroots campaigns of the 1950s underwent several transformations. Some groups shifted their focus to Morton Sobell, the other defendant in the case. In 1973, the Rosenbergs' two sons, Michael and Robert Meeropol, continued the work of the NCSJRC, forming the National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case (NCRRC). A major initial focus of the organization was the release, under the Freedom of Information Act, of the FBI files on the Rosenbergs. The Meeropols sued the FBI and in 1975 won the release of hundreds of thousands of previously secret documents pertaining to their parents' case. The NCRRC sought to exonerate Julius and Ethel from the charge of atomic espionage and prove their innocence, and push for recognition from the United States government that the judicial system had not given the Rosenbergs due process. From the mid-1970s to the early 2000s, the NCRRC continued to seek an official review of the Rosenberg case and the exoneration of the couple through outreach and publicity campaigns and events.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains materials spanning the years 1944-2005, with the bulk of material dating from 1974-1997. The vast majority of materials in the collection were created in the process of outreach and publicity work, and include correspondence and promotional materials. To a lesser extent, there are administrative records such as meeting minutes, agendas, and memos; event planning documents; fundraising reports; local committee materials (including finance reports, correspondence, and promotional material); donor cards; and financial reports. A large chunk of the administrative materials pertain to the Carnegie Hall events coordinated by the Committee, primarily the 1974 event which kickstarted the efforts of the Committee.
Of the promotional materials, there are materials related to distributable printed matter such as newsletters, press releases, news bulletins, pamphlets and booklets, posters, buttons, event flyers and programs, advertisements, invitations, book reviews, speeches, a sermon, correspondence, and their respective drafts, mock-ups, and notes. There are also research files or collected materials used for the process of creating promotional materials. These include materials such as court transcripts, FOIA documents, newspaper clippings, correspondence, newsletters and promotional materials from other organizations, transcripts of public appearances, interview transcripts, photographic prints, photographic negatives, and copies of website text. Related to these promotional materials and research files are works and publications created in response to, or inspired by, the Rosenberg case. These include plays, an opera, music, manuscripts, theses, poems, and books from writers, researchers, and students. These artistic and academic creations include manuscripts, bound materials, cassette tapes, audio CDs, vinyl records, and a VHS tape.
Jewish communists -- United States.; Espionage, Soviet -- United States.; Jewish communists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Trials (Sedition); Communists -- United States.; Civil rights workers.; Civil rights.; Cold War.; Capital punishment.; Fair trial; Rosenberg, Ethel, 1915-1953; Rosenberg, Julius, 1918-1953; Hittner, Daniel; National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case; Meeropol, Michael; Meeropol, Robert; Katz, Aaron; Sobell, Morton; Greenglass, David, 1922-2014; Alman, Emily Arnow; Alman, David, 1919-; Kaufman, Irving R. (Irving Robert), 1910-1992; Center for Constitutional Rights (New York, N.Y.); Rosenberg Fund for Children; National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (U.S.); Abu-Jamal, Mumia
- Series I. Administrative and Financial Records, 1974-1988; 1974-1976; 1.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by subject. The local committees portion of the series is alphabetized.
  Scope and Contents
  The majority of materials in this series relate to the Carnegie Hall events that the Committee coordinated early in the history of the organization. The 1974 Carnegie Hall event is predominantly documented. This series also contains financial reports, committee agendas, minutes, and memos, and local committee materials.
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, American Program Bureau, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - Public Service Announcements, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - City Star, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, National Lawyers Guild, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - Daily World, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - Guardian Hand Out, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Hall: Morning Freiheit Ad and Story, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - N.Y. Law Journal, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - N.Y. Times, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad - Staten Island Advance, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Hall: News, Philadelphia Bulletin, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, $50 Ticket Letter, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, Abbot's Thank You Letter 3/24/74, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, FLASH!, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, Thank-You to Contributors, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, Requests for Greetings, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, Mailing List, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, Personal Thank-You's, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ads, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Hall: Mailings, Acceptances, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Carnegie Hall: Other Returns, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Carnegie Hall: NY State Returns, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carnegie Hall: NYC Returns, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Carnegie Hall: Invitations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Carnegie Hall: Releases and Flyers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Carnegie Hall: Press Kits, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - C.H. Flyers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Carnegie Hall: Running Order, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Emily's Speech, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Booking Facts, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Script, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Carnegie Hall: Pete Seeger, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Ticket Pricing, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Robby's Speech, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Glossies, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Cast & Production address, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Notes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Photos, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Programs, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Program Copy Samples, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Rehearsals, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Script Permission, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Carnegie Hall: Production - Seating Capacity, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Carnegie Hall: Big Black, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Carnegie Hall: Balfour Brickner, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Carnegie Hall: Shirley Graham Du Bois, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Carnegie Hall: Philip Morrison, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Carnegie Hall: Fyke Farmer, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ring Lardner, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Carnegie Hall: Linus Pauling, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Carnegie Hall: Brock Peters, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Carnegie Hall: Harold C. Urey, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Carnegie Hall: Bella Abzug, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Carnegie Hall 75 Ticket Pricing, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Carnegie Hall Corp., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Carnegie Hall: Media (Releases, etc), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Carnegie Hall Script, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - C.H. Expenses, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Carnegie Hall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - C.H.: Meeting (Steve), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Program C.H. 1976 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - C.H. 1976 - Flyers (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - C.H. - Publicity (mostly free), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - CH: Spot Announcements - Radio, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Carnegie Hall: Ad Orders, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - C.H.: Media Free Tickets & Passes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Carnegie Hall: Messages of Support for Program, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Carnegie Hall, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Carnegie Hall Release - May 6 '76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Staff, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - H.S. Brochures, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Fund Raising Ideas, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Fund-raising Ideas/Action, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Fund-raising Ideas for Summer and Survival 5/76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Fund Raising to Big Donors (M), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - How to Do Publicity (Nat'l Conf), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Musical Entertainment List, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Les Baltimore, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Memo from Steve, 12/16/75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Minutes Mailing of 5/27/76 Post-Boston, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Steve: Progress Report Since Boston - May 19 Letter for Minutes, etc., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Steve Laver, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Housing Form - Cambridge, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Set Reg. Form and Envelopes for Nat'l Comm. Mtg. April, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Steve Letter - April 24-25 Nat'l Comm. Meeting - Boston, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Rutgers-Bills, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Loans, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Finance Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Steering Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Steering Committee, General Memos, etc., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Steering Committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Meeting 11/29/75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Nat'l Comm. Mtg. Agenda 11/12 - 11/15, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - National Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Ethical Culture Meeting 6/75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Reports, Research, and Other Administrative Materials, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence, Staff and Financial Reports, Fund for Open Information and Accountability, Inc., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - 25th Anniversary Committee Materials, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for the 25th Anniversary, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Congressional Schedule, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Selected Media List for Special Info, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Press (National) from Media Cards, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Organizations List, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - List of Daily Newspapers & Weekly, Semi-Weekly and Tri-Weekly, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Congress (House & Senate) Lists, circa 1975 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - VIP Lists, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Sponsors, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Congressional Phone Directory, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Big Contributors List, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Additions to In-House Mailing for NCRRC, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Key New Contacts, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Mailing List, circa 1976 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Sponsors, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Contacts Outside Local Areas, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Congressional List, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Finance: Bills, Appeals, Local Comms, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local Newsletters, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local Committees, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local Committee Output, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Affiliate: Amherst, Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Affiliate: Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Atlanta CRRC, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Affiliate: Baltimore, Maryland, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Affiliate: Boston, Massachusetts, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boston Fundraiser 3/28/76, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Boston Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Boston CRRC, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Affiliate: Bucks-Mercer, Pa. NJ, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Party Invitation and Raffle, Bucks-Mercer Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Local Committee Event, Bucks County, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Affiliate: Buffalo, N.Y., circa 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Affiliate: Chicago, Illinois, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chicago CRRC, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Cincinnati CRRC, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cleveland CRRC, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Affiliate: Detroit, Michigan, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Affiliate: Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Florida Comm., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Los Angeles CRRC, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Madison Local Comm., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Affiliate: New Haven, Connecticut, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - New York Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - NY Committee Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - NY Volunteers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - New N.Y. Comm., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - N.Y. Committee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Affiliate: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Leaflet for Phila. 12/8/74, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Phila. Newsletter, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Philadelphia CRRC, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bay Area/West Coast Comm., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - San Francisco-East Bay CRRC, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Long Island CRRC, circa 1977 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Affiliate: Springfield, Mass., 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Texas (Hank et al) Local Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Affiliate: Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Washington CRRC, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Donor Cards, circa 1974-1976 (Box 18)
- Series II. Correspondence, 1974-2004; 1974-1985; 4.75 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 1 card box.
  Original groupings of materials were retained where evident (e.g. alphabetically, by year, and by state/country). The geographical grouping is alphabetized. If not a part of these groupings, materials were arranged chronologically.
  This series consists of correspondence between the NCRRC and their supporters, sponsors and donors, committee members, local committees, institutions, and news outlets.
  - Chron File Sept. 1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Chron File Oct 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Chron File Nov 1974 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Chron File December 1974 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Chron Jan, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Chron Feb, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Chron March, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Chron April, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Chron May, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Chron June, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Chron July, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Chron August, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Chron September 1975 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Chron October, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Chron November, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Chron December, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - 1975 File (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 1975 Letters (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 64-66)
  - Committee Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence & Put on Mailing List, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mailings and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1979, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13-16)